http://www.brucemore.org/privacy-policy/

Membership
Sign up for a membership today!
Email List Signup
Join our Email List today!
Home > Privacy Policy
Tweet
Privacy Policy of Brucemore, Inc.
Revised as of April 1, 2018
Brucemore, Inc. (“Brucemore”) is committed to the protection of your privacy while on our website. Brucemore does not collect personal information such as names, email addresses, mailing addresses unless you knowingly choose to provide that information to us.
Policy on Information Collection
Brucemore collects personal information for ticket purchases, memberships, donations, program registrations, electronic newsletters and mailings, and general inquiries. This information is used only for the intended services. For some of these services, Brucemore may request information about background, occupation, demographics, and interests.
This website automatically collects information about computer hardware and software. This can include IP addresses, browser types, domain names, access times, and the referring websites that visitors use to access this website. The site uses this information to maintain the quality of the service while you are on the website, as well as to collect general statistics about the site.
Policy on Information Disclosure
This website collects personal information to operate the site and to deliver the services you request. This information helps Brucemore understand our audience to allow us to better meet the needs of website users. Brucemore will not sell, trade, or rent personal information. We may compile aggregate statistics and provide them to third parties, but these statistics will not include information that identifies individual website users.
Brucemore may save personal information to comply with federal and state policies, but we will not disclose this information to third parties or government agencies unless we are required to do so by state or federal law or we must act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of our users or the public.
Revisions to the Privacy Policy
The privacy policy may be revised at any time. We may revise the policy in response to changes in the law or other factors. We encourage website users to periodically visit this page to review the most current policy.
Right to Opt Out
You have the right to “opt-out” of certain uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this website and/or through our Services, you have the opportunity to elect to, or not to, receive promotional correspondence from Brucemore.
You may also opt-out of Brucemore e-mails by clicking on an opt-out link (SafeUnsubscribe) at the bottom of the promotional correspondence you receive. Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving promotional e-mails from Brucemore, we may still contact you by e-mail in connection with your account with us or to provide you with important information about Brucemore, this Website or the Services.
If you have any questions regarding our information privacy practices or wish to opt out, please contact Brucemore.
Security
Brucemore takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever Brucemore collects sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the website.
While Brucemore uses encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Links to other website
The website of Brucemore, Inc. may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave Brucemore’s site, you should note that Brucemore does not have any control over that other website. Therefore, Brucemore cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, contact us.
Sign up for a membership today!
Email List Signup
Join our Email List today!
© Copyright 2020 Brucemore. All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy | 2160 Linden Drive, SE., Cedar Rapids, IA 52403 | 319-362-7375
Powered by
Metro Studios
